# Alisha Bhale

Software Engineer with industry experience of 2.9 years Skilled in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Conversational AI, and frameworks like Angular and backbone. Played a key role in systems development and maintenance life cycle for desktop applications. Hardworking, inquisitive, and dependable team member with proven leadership skills.

alisha.bhale@gmail.com



#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Front-end Developer **EIS Pvt Ltd**

01/2022 - Present

Provides e-platform to maintain documentation forms and audits

- Lead team to develop and deploy a feature from scratch
- Lead Module development and technical documentation maintenance and HLD development.

# **Program Analyst Trainee**

Cognizant Technology Solutions

06/2021 - 12/2022

Providing technology solutions

- Efficient designing and testing of Al-Powered Chatbots.
- Successful production deployment of new features and contribution in scrum activities

# Associate Developer Simply Compete Pvt Ltd

06/2020 - 05/2021

Providing sports and education platform

- Developed a highly responsive user-interface serving autocomplete search components via Angular concepts with creating efficient technical documentation.
- Refactored and redesigned the user interface for the event operations of the sports platform.
- Refactored the guiz-related functionality and database for education and sports platform resulting in 40% code reduction.

#### **CERTIFICATES**

Certified AI Professional - NIELIT

Conversational AI Bot development - Kore.ai

Digital marketing in analytics in practice - Google

Agile project management - Google

### **EDUCATION**

### **B.E Computer Engineering**

VIIT, Pune, India

2017 - 2020 8.08

# Diploma in Computer Engineering

Government Polytechnic Aurangabad

2014 - 2017 90.12

# **SKILLS**



#### PROJECT & PUBLICATION

Test Case Management Tool. (Sponsored by Ivavsys Pvt. Ltd.)

A web application providing an efficient way of managing the testing process and calculate the complexity of test cases.

Published paper on test case management tool in Science and Engineering Research Support Society. (APR-2020)

http://www.sersc.org/journals/index.php/IJFGCN/article/view/29227

#### Smart Garbage Management System

Arduino based system to give the real-time garbage level status of the dustbin

#### **EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

Contribution in organizing 3rd national level conference on "Recent trends in Engineering and Technology",Vishwacon'19.

Technical documentation head of techno-cultural event, Gandharva'19 VIIT.

Article published in college's yearly magazine, Lighthouse 2019.

Publicity and documentation head of IoT forum, VIIT.

Core committee member CSI, VIIT.

#### **LANGUAGES**

Enalish Professional Working Proficiency

Hindi Professional Working Proficiency

Marathi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency